$F4NV_Goodsprings	Goodsprings

$F4NV_Neutral	Neutral
$F4NV_Accepted	Accepted
$F4NV_Liked	Liked
$F4NV_Idolized	Idolized
$F4NV_Shunned	Shunned
$F4NV_Mixed	Mixed
$F4NV_Smiling Troublemaker	Smiling Troublemaker
$F4NV_Good-Natured Rascal	Good-Natured Rascal
$F4NV_Hated	Hated
$F4NV_Sneering Punk	Sneering Punk
$F4NV_Unpredictable	Unpredictable
$F4NV_Dark Hero	Dark Hero
$F4NV_Vilified	Vilified
$F4NV_Merciful Thug	Merciful Thug
$F4NV_Soft-Hearted Devil	Soft-Hearted Devil
$F4NV_Wild Child	Wild Child

$F4NV_DESC_Neutral	People don't know enough about you to form an opinion.
$F4NV_DESC_Accepted	Folks have come to accept you for your helpful nature.
$F4NV_DESC_Liked	Enough news of your good works has been passed around that people like you.
$F4NV_DESC_Idolized	Renowned for your extensive support and goodwill, you are idolized by the community.
$F4NV_DESC_Shunned	You've left a poor impression on the community and may be shunned as a result.
$F4NV_DESC_Mixed	A little bit good mixed with a little bit bad, people haven't figured you out yet.
$F4NV_DESC_Smiling Troublemaker	People know you're good at heart even though you're occasionally a troublemaker.
$F4NV_DESC_Good-Natured Rascal	Your reputation as a good-natured friend of the community manages to outshine your dark side.
$F4NV_DESC_Hated	Now that folks know you're bad, most people outright hate you.
$F4NV_DESC_Sneering Punk	Even though you've done some good for the community, people still think you're a punk.
$F4NV_DESC_Unpredictable	No one's sure what to make of your unpredictable nature, but you've left a strong impression.
$F4NV_DESC_Dark Hero	Folks still think you're some kind of hero, but you sure can be nasty sometimes.
$F4NV_DESC_Vilified	For your overwhelmingly monstrous behavior, you have become vilified by the community.
$F4NV_DESC_Merciful Thug	Despite your reputation as a thug, you are known to occasionally show a charitable side.
$F4NV_DESC_Soft-Hearted Devil	Most people say you're the devil himself, but most admit you've also done a world of good.
$F4NV_DESC_Wild Child	Your wild, seemingly capricious behavior leaves people scratching their heads in confusion and avoiding close contact.